salarylist.com 2013-05-24

# Privacy Policy | SalaryList.com

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Date of Last Revision: May 10, 2012

**Your privacy is our top concern.** We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy: 

A. We do not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.

B. We do not share your contact information with another User without your consent.

C. Any personally identifiable information that you provide will be secured with industry standard protocols and technology.

**SalaryList.com Privacy Policy Highlights**

This page summarizes the key highlights from our privacy policy. By using SalaryList.com and other JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, you represent that you are 13 years old or older and you consent to the information collection and use practices described herein. For more information, read our full privacy policy below.

**Personal information collected**

We collect information:

When you register an account to become a user (“User”), such as your name, e-mail, country, location and a password.

When you add to your profile with further information about yourself or your private contacts.

We use cookies and other technologies to recognize you, customize your experience and serve advertisements.

We automatically receive from your internet use such information as your IP address, the URLs of sites from which you arrive or leave the JobsAndCareer.com Network websites, your type of browser and your ISP.

**Uses of personal information**

We use the information you provide to:

Administer your account with us and customize the service we provide to you.

To send you service or promotional communications through email and notices on the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites.

We do not sell, rent or otherwise provide your personal identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes.

We provide you with the means to control whether or not your contact information is shared with another User.

In order to deliver our services, we may share information with third parties.

Enable you to share your information and communicate with other Users, or provide (usually at your option) your personal details to third parties offering combined services with JobsAndCareer.com Network sites.

**Your information choices**

You can:

Review, enhance or edit your personal information through your account settings page.

Choose what information you make available through your public profile.

Control the messages you receive from JobsAndCareer.com Network and other Users and how these messages are sent.

Change your settings to control visibility and accessibility through our website.

Tell us to close your JobsAndCareer.com Network sites account.

**Security**

Personal information you provide will be secured with industry standards and technology.

**How to contact us**

If you have any questions or comments please contact us (Attn: Privacy Policy).

====================

**SalaryList.com Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. By continuing to use SalaryList.com service and other JobAndCareer.com Network sites after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, you are consenting to the changes.

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:

·        What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by JobsAndCareer.com Network sites.

·        How the information is used.

·        With whom the information may be shared.

·        How you can access and change your account settings.

·        What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by JobsAndCareer.com Network sites.

·        How to contact us.

1\. Personal Information Collected

The purpose of the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites is to permit Users to voluntarily share jobs and career related information for the purposes of achieving jobs satisfaction and career success. You willingly provide us certain personal information, which we collect in order to allow you to benefit from the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. If you have any hesitation about providing such information to us and/or having such information displayed on the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, you should not become a member of the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites community.

We collect your personal information in the following ways:

1.1 Registration

In order to become a User, you must first create an account on our website. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information, which you recognize and expressly acknowledge is personal information allowing others, including JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, to identify you: name, email address, country, ZIP/postal code, a brief summary of your background, and a password chosen by you.

1.2 Profile Information

Once you become a User, you may provide additional information describing your skills, professional experiences, and career objectives. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration to become a User is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities in the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites system to build and leverage our career network. Any information you provide at registration or in the Profile section that is not personally identifiable may be used in the same manner and extent to which other information that is not personally identifiable is permitted to be used hereunder, including for the purpose of serving advertisements through the service. If you opt-out you may lose the potential benefit of being a User, including receiving ads that are more targeted to your interests.

1.3 Contacts Information

In order to invite others to connect with you directly in JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, you may use the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites services to invite them if they are a User, or enter their names and email addresses. This information will be used by JobsAndCareer.com Network sites to send your invitation including a message that you write. The names and email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation and reminders.

You may also choose to manually enter or upload data about your contacts into your account settings section of the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. You may not invite anyone to connect with you whom you do not know. All information entered there will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites without your permission. All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own information.

1.4 Customer Service

JobsAndCareer.com Network sites may collect information through the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites in order to, among other things, accurately categorize and respond to a customer’s inquiry and deliver appropriate service levels.

1.5 Cookies

Like most websites, JobsAndCareer.com Network sites use cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows JobsAndCareer.com Network sites to recognize you as a User when you return to the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites using the same computer and web browser. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on our website.

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your JobsAndCareer.com Network sites account. The next time you visit the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing User so you will not need to log in before using the service. In order to access or change any of your private information or to send a message to another User, however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie.

Additionally, if you log out of the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing User preferences and tracking User trends. In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing services to our Users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through such cookies will not be personally identifiable but may provide general segment information, e.g. your industry or geographic location, your occupation, or information about your professional or educational background, for greater customization of your user experience. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies or you opt to refuse all cookies, you may not be able to use the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites or services. JobsAndCareer.com Network sites do not store personally identifiable information in the cookies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>. (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> .) The cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on JobsAndcCareer.com Network sites. You can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please read Google ad and content network privacy policy.

1.6 Log Files, IP Addresses and Information about Your Computer

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, email patterns, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is not shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

1.7 Consent toJobsAndCareer.com Network Sites Processing Information about You

Certain information you provide to JobsAndCareer.com Network sites may reveal, or allow others to identify, your nationality, ethnic origin, religion or other aspects of your private life, and more generally about you. Please be aware that in providing information to JobsAndCareer.com Network sites for the purposes of opening your user account, you are expressly and voluntarily accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and JobsAndCareer.com Network sites’ Terms of Use. The supplying of all such information by you to JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, including all information deemed “sensitive” by applicable law, is entirely voluntary on your part. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, but please note that your withdrawal of consent will not be retroactive.

1.8 Rights to Access, Correct and Eliminate Information about You

You have a right to access, modify, correct and eliminate the data about you which has been collected pursuant to your decision to become a User. If you update any of your information, we may keep a copy of the information which you originally provided to us in our archives for uses documented herein.

We take your rights seriously and encourage you to use them if you deem this to be appropriate. You may exercise these rights by contacting us (Attn: Privacy Policy)

2\. Uses of Personal Information

JobsAndCareer.com Network sites are online service dedicated to helping peoples more effectively connect with one another to achieve job satisfaction and career success. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on our websites is used to help you describe yourself to other Users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by JobsAndCareer.com Network sites from Users (such as, for example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. This information can be utilized by JobsAndCareer.com Network sites in such manner as JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

2.1 JobsAndCareer.com Network Sites Communications

JobsAndCareer.com Network sites will communicate with you through email and notices posted on the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites or through other means available through the service, including text and other forms of messaging. If we send any communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with any such access (including text messaging charges for messages to your mobile device). These include a series of up to three welcome emails which help inform new Users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from JobsAndCareer.com Network sites related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another User in your network sends you an opportunity. JobsAndCareer.com Network sites may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. You can change your e-mail and contact preferences at any time by logging into your account settings and amending your email notification choices. If you wish, you can also opt-out of receiving promotional emails, by contacting us.

2.2 Customized Content

Information provided to JobsAndCareer.com Network sites (or to third parties with whom it offers combined services) is also used to customize your experience on our website. For example, when you login to your account we will display the screen names of new Users who have recently followed you.

2.3 Sharing Information with Third Parties

JobsAndCareer.com Network sites take the privacy of Users very seriously. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions or to provide specific services or information.

JobsAndCareer.com Network sites offer a “public profile” feature which allows Users to publish portions of their JobsAndCareer.com Network sites profile, including their “name”, but not their “email address” to the public Internet. Users may opt-out of this feature by contacting us, however JobsAndCareer.com Network sites do not warrant how often third-party search engines will update their cache.

We may provide aggregated anonymous data about the usage of our services to third parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including to prospective advertisers on JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. We may segment our Users by role (i.e. interview coach, career center), industry, geographic location, or company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our Users’ activities on the site, please contact us.

2.4 Surveys and Polls

As a User, you will receive requests to participate in market research including polls and surveys submitted by other JobsAndCareer.com Network sites members. If you participate in surveys and polls offered through our website, the information you provide may be visible to others using the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. You may opt-out of participating by contacting us to stop receiving these inquiries and requests.

2.5 Forums/Chats/Blogs

If you post on the Answers section of JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, or use a bulletin board, import a blog, or participate in a chat room on JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you choose to provide there can be read, collected, or used by other Users of these forums, as well as other third parties, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. JobsAndCareer.com Network sites are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

2.6 Communications to Other Users

Many emails you initiate through JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, e.g., an invitation sent to a non-User, will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many answers you have provided), but will not list the people to whom you’re directly connected. Other communications that you initiate through the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, like a private message, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another User if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other.

2.7 Legal Disclaimer

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, such as responses to civil or criminal subpoenas, or other requests by law enforcement personnel. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, subpoena, or other legal process or request to JobsAndCareer.com Network sites brought in any country throughout the world, or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

2.8 Disclosures to Others

We may also disclose your personal and other information you provide, to another third party as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of a JobsAndCareer.com Network site or company. Any third party to which we transfer or sell JobsAndCareer.com’s assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us.

3\. Your Information Choices

3.1 Accessing and Changing Your Account Information

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information you publish, or to the settings for your JobsAndCareer.com Network sites account including your email, and contact preferences, at any time by logging in to your account on the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, JobsAndCareer.com Network sites may, for a time, retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database.

3.2 Closing Your Account

You can also close your account through the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. If you close your JobsAndCareer.com Network sites account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable database. We may retain certain data contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, please contact us. You will receive an email response to account closing requests. Please send your reply using an email account that you have registered with JobsAndCareer.com Network sites under your name.

4\. Your Obligations

As a User, you have certain obligations toward the other Users with whom you will be communicating. Certain of these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and others have become commonplace in user-friendly communities of like-minded members, such as JobsAndCareer.com Network sites:

You must, at all times, respect the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights which may belong to third parties (such as photographs).

You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information which may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic or which may otherwise violate the purpose and spirit of JobsAndCareer.com Network sites and its community of Users.

You must not provide information to JobsAndCareer.com Network sites and /or other Users which you believe might be injurious or detrimental to your person, professional or social status.

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account by JobsAndCareer.com Network sites, as we take these principles seriously and consider them to be the basis on which our Users adhere to the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites and the services which it offers.

5\. Important Information

5.1 Children

Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

5.2 Changes to this Privacy Policy

JobsAndCareer.com Network sites may update this privacy policy at any time, with or without advance notice. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites or send you an email, as provided for above. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

If you use the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

6\. Security

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on JobsAndCareer.com Network sites is password-protected when it is exchanged between your web browser and the JobsAndCareer.com Network sites. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and we use a tier-one secured-access data center. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. Please note that emails and instant messaging and similar means of communication with other users of JobsAndCareer.com Network sites are not encrypted and we strongly request you not to communicate any confidential information through these means.

7\. How to contact us

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact us (Attn: Privacy Policy).
